{
	"Rows": 
	[
		{
			"RowName": "Pumpkinvale_SecretaryIntro",
			"StringProperty": "$Flustered$Oh um excuse me, are you *PlayerName*? $SmileTalkingTessa$ *~Wave*My name is *NpcName* I was sent to welcome you, so um, welcome to *TownName*! $SmileTalkingTessa$ I’m so happy you’re here, we’ve been needing another farmer for a while now. $SmileTalkingTessa$ Exporting produce is the town’s main source of income that we need for development.  $SmileTalkingTessa$ As promised in the ad, we'll be giving you a major discount on the property. $Flustered$ *~Disagree* I’m so sorry, am I rambling? I’m rambling again aren’t I? $LeSighLashes$ I'm so sorry... $LeSighLashes$ I wanted to show you around town, but I must return to the office. $SmileTalkingTessa$ Oh, here's a map of the town to help you get around. $SmileTalkingTessa$ *~HeadNod* When you’re done looking at the map please come by the mayor’s office. $SmileTalking$ *~Wave* Ok, see you."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "PumpkinVale_SecretaryGoodbye",
			"StringProperty": "Oh shoot! Speaking of missing deadlines there was something I needed to do for the mayor! So sorry I could not chat more. See you later."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "PumpkinVale_MayorIntro",
			"StringProperty": "*~Wave* $JulianTalking$ Why, hellloooo there. $JulianTalking$ You must be *PlayerName*. $JulianTalking$ I'm so excited to see you here. $JulianTalking$ I'm sure you are eager to start exploring the town, so let me get you set up."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "PumpkinVale_MayorExplainVoucher",
			"StringProperty": "*~HeadNod* $JulianTalking$ The property ticket lets you get the land on a loan. $JulianTalking$ You will have to pay it back, before you are able to expand. $JulianTalking$ Don't worry, you can take your time paying it back. $JulianTalking$ There is an ATM at the post office on Fawn's Apple Lane where you can pay off any debt. $JulianTalking$ All right, go right ahead and pick which property you would like. $JulianTalking$ You can't change it later, so make sure you pick the one you want."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "PumpkinVale_MayorPickedPlot",
			"StringProperty": "$JulianTalking$ Oh, here is a bed for your house. $JulianTalking$ If you're not sure how to place it, Vera at the furniture store can tell you how to decorate your house with furniture. $JulianTalking$ Make sure you sleep for enough hours to recover your energy after working. $JulianTalking$ Oh, I also asked some of the townsfolk to show you how you can make some extra money with other skills. $JulianTalking$ I'm also going to give you a chest to store some of your items. $JulianTalking$ Hmmm, there's quite a bit for you to learn so...  $JulianTalking$ Here, take this journal. $JulianTalking$ *~HeadNod* You can use it to keep track of everything. $JulianTalking$ Today you can take your time getting used to the town. $JulianTalking$  It's important for you to get your farm started, so please complete most of the tasks in the journal before you leave town to go exploring. $JulianTalking$ I will send you a farming quota in the mail and it will be added to your journal as well. $JulianTalking$ What’s the farming quota, you ask? $JulianTalking$ Well, every season I’ll send you a list of crops the town needs you to grow. $JulianTalking$  For each item on the list that you complete, I'll send you a bonus payment in the mail.  $JulianTalking$ Oh my, look at me prattling on. $JulianTalking$ Make sure to check the mail when you get a chance. $JulianTalking$ *~HeadNod* Off you go now. $JulianTalking$ Remember to complete enough tasks in the journal and ship some crops before travelling outside of town."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "PumpkinVale_Step3InvClosed_After",
			"StringProperty": "$JulianTalking$ Do you have the property ticket with you? $JulianTalking$ Check your bag, to see if you remembered to bring it. $JulianTalking$ I also have some things to give you as well."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "PumpkinVale_Step4InvClosed_Before",
			"StringProperty": "It looks like you do have your property ticket."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "PumpkinVale_Step4InvOpen_Before",
			"StringProperty": "I see that you have a property voucher in your inventory."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_2",
			"StringProperty": "You must be *PlayerName*. I am *NpcName* the secretary and I was sent to greet you. You don’t look like much of a farmer to me. I suppose we cannot be picky if we want to meet our export demands. I suppose you will do peasant. Here is a map to assist you in getting around town. When you are done looking at the map, come to mayor’s office immediately to get your farm deed. Do not keep us waiting. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_3",
			"StringProperty": "Hi *PlayerName*, I'm so excited to see you here. I'm sure you are eager to start exploring the town and checking out your new farm."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_4",
			"StringProperty": "*~HeadNod*The voucher let's you get the land on a loan. You will have to pay it back, before you decide to expand. Alright, go right ahead and pick which one you would like.You can't change it later, so make sure you pick the one you want."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_5",
			"StringProperty": "Good choice, here is the deed. *~TakeItemFromPocket*Here, I will mark where to find the plot on your map. *~TakeItemFromPocket*Here is a bed as a welcome gift. Congratulations and welcome to *TownName* I hope you make a good life here! Everyone's really friendly so be sure to say hi. Before you go off wandering too far make sure you finish some of them there tasks on your journal alright."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_Step3InvClosed_After",
			"StringProperty": "Now I'm sure you're eager to get started so let me get that property voucher for your new land."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_Step4InvClosed_Before",
			"StringProperty": "That's what I'm talking about."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_Step4InvOpen_Before",
			"StringProperty": "I see that you have a property voucher in your inventory."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Pumpkinvale_SecretaryExplainCompass",
			"StringProperty": "The diamond is where you need to go. You can also use your compass to help guide you, so you don't have to keep your map open. Look for the marker and it'll show you if you need to go North, South, East or West."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Pumpkinvale_SecretaryExplainJournal",
			"StringProperty": "Do you have a journal to make a notes?"
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Pumpkinvale_SecretaryJournalOpened",
			"StringProperty": "If you want to explore around town first you can make a note in your journal. I'm pretty forgetful, so I rely on keeping notes all the time. Use the journal to see what tasks you need to do. Some tasks may have deadlines so make sure you keep track of that too. The mayor gets annoyed at me when I accidentally miss my deadlines. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_SecretaryIntro",
			"StringProperty": "$SeriousTalkingMelanie$ You must be *PlayerName*. $SeriousTalkingMelanie$ I am *NpcName* the secretary and I was sent to greet you. $SeriousTalkingMelanie$ You don’t look like much of a farmer to me. $SeriousTalkingMelanie$ I suppose we cannot be picky if we want to meet our export demands. $SeriousTalkingMelanie$ I suppose you will do. $SeriousTalkingMelanie$ Here is a map to assist you in getting around town. $SeriousTalkingMelanie$ When you are done looking at the map, come to mayor’s office immediately to get your farm deed. $SeriousTalkingMelanie$ Do not keep us waiting. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_SecretaryGoodbye",
			"StringProperty": "Do not keep us waiting. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_MayorIntro",
			"StringProperty": "Well, look at who's here. The new farmer I take it right? Welcome to Wahoo Beach young buck. My name is Mayor Lamonte and I run this here town. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_MayorExplainVoucher",
			"StringProperty": "Go ahead and pick which plot you want now."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Wahoo_Beach_MayorPickedPlot",
			"StringProperty": "Nice choice. So the payment is only 1000g for that there lot, but you can take your time with the payment. If you go to the post office on the shore, there's an ATM where you can pay off your debts. In fact there is quite a bit you're going to need to learn, right? I'm gunna give ya a pocket journal where you can keep track of everything you need. I will also write down some townsfolk you should see who can teach you what you need to know around there. I'm also giving you a bed and some other things to start off with. Pretty sweet deal, right? One more thing young buck, your farming quota. I'll send you a letter on the first of each month with some items we need shipped for that month. For each item you complete I'll send a bonus payment for them. So, keep a look out for that tomorrow ya'hear? Hopefully, if we increase our exports we can help keep that darn Jounce Corp\\. off of this island. The worst, I tell ya what. Sorry, a bit off topic there. Don't go off wandering too far before you ship some produce and see those, townsfolk ya hear? Hurry along now. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_SecretaryIntro",
			"StringProperty": "*~Wave* According to my paperwork you must be the new farmer *PlayerName*. I'm sure you're exhausted climbing all the way up here. Oh, where are my manners? Welcome to Diamond Falls, my name is *NpcName*, the secretary to the mayor of Diamond Falls.Before you head to the mayor's office, I need to give you a map. Once you're done looking at the map come to mayor's office right away and talk to Mayor Fukuyama and she'll get you set up. After you speak with her then you can explore around town."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_SecretaryGoodbye",
			"StringProperty": "*~Wave* Take your time, see you later."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_MayorIntro",
			"StringProperty": "*~Haughty* HELLO THERE! You must be *PlayerName*. It's a pleasure to meet you! My name is Fukuyama and I'm the mayor of Diamond Falls. We're a strong mining town, with plenty of ores and fossils to be found. You scared of bugs? It's too cold up here so you'll find none, it's great, HAHAHA! *ShowAhem* Sorry about that, let's get down to business. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_MayorExplainVoucher",
			"StringProperty": "Let's get your property ticket. That ticket lets you get your first farm at a discount! You'll need to pay back the loan on the farm at the post office ATM. You can't buy more structures or property until you do. No problem though, you can pay it off at your own pace. Let's take a look at the farm plots available. You can't change it later so make sure you pick one that sounds appealing. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_MayorPickedPlot",
			"StringProperty": "NICE! I have some items to get you started. If you're not sure how to place furniture on your farm you can talk to Joshua at the furniture shop. He'll show you how to place and arrange things around your farm. While it may be tempting to hit the ground running and do all the things, make sure to watch your stamina. Take a nap on the bed to rest up and recover some energy. The longer you sleep the more energy you'll recover. I've asked some of the residents here to teach you some more skills to help you settle in and make more money. Here, take this journal. I've written down a list of residents and tasks you should complete before exploring too far from town. I'll also be sending you a farming quota in the mail. You don't have to complete everything, but you'll get a bonus payment by shipping the crops requested on the quota. Are you overwhelmed yet! HAHAHAHA! It's not that bad I promise. Check your inventory, check your journal, check your map, and you'll figure everything out. Remember, ship some crops and complete most of the tasks before you wander off too far from town. "
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_Step3InvClosed",
			"StringProperty": "You remembered to bring your property ticket right? Check your bag."
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_Step4InvOpen_Before",
			"StringProperty": "I see that you have a property voucher in your inventory!"
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_Step4InvClosed_Before",
			"StringProperty": "EXCELLENT!"
		},
		{
			"RowName": "Diamond_Falls_Step3InvClosed_After",
			"StringProperty": " Do you have the property ticket with you? Check your bag."
		}
	]
}